### PANGESTU RISKI LESTARI, S.T

#### Front-End Developer

Cengkareng, Jakarta | 0822-9806-3323 | riskilestaripangestu@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/pangesturl

#### PROFILE SUMMARY

I am currently diving deep into front-end development through an intensive bootcamp. I am committed to building my expertise in:

HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, React.js and Git.

With my background and passion for learning, I aim to deliver creative and efficient solutions in web development. I believe that the combination of technical skills, dedication, and curiosity is the key to succeeding in the tech industry.

#### **EDUCATION**

Aug 2015 - Aug 2019

#### Bachelor of Agricultural Engineering, BRAWIJAYA UNIVERSITY

- Graduated with a 3.44 GPA.
- Thesis: Ultraviolet (UV)-Ultrasonic Application on the Quality of Coconut Milk.

#### EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Feb 2022 - Present

#### PT. SURI NUSANTARA JAYA (Retail), Administrator Staff

- Oversaw finances, expenses, and billing.
- Make sales reports and stock items from online store
- Manage online store sales
- Respond to customer criticism and suggestions

Jan 2017 - Jan 2018

#### BRAWIJAYA UNIVERSITY (Education), Laboratory assistant,

- · Laboratory Assistant for Biomaterials Course
- Material Strength Subject Laboratory Assistant
- Laboratory Assistant for Basic Physics Courses
- Laboratory Assistant for Environmental Measurement, Electronics & Instrumentation Courses

#### **ACHIEVEMENT**

2013 2nd Indonesian International Invention Festival (I3F), IYSA - Malang

Gold Medal of Food Technology Category

2017 3rd Teuku Umar Awards Aceh, Universitas Teuku Umar - Banda Aceh

1st Place of Innovative Product Category Based on Agriculture and

Fisheries

2018 1st Indonesian International Invention Festival (I3F), IYSA - Malang

Gold Medal of Technology Innovation Category

2018 3rd National Student Seminar on Agriculture Technology,

UGM -Yogyakarta

Best Idea of Paper Technical Presentation

| SKILLS        | HTML 5 & CSS<br>Javascript<br>React Js<br>Git  | Beginner<br>Beginner<br>Beginner<br>Beginner | Microsoft Excel<br>Sales Software<br>RDMS (Sql Query)<br>Microsoft office | Expert<br>Expert<br>Skillful<br>Expert                 |
|---------------|--|--|---|--|
| CERTIFICATION | Food Safety Management System (ISO 22000:2018)  Hazard Analysis and Critical Control Points (HACCP)  Good Manufacturing Practices (GMP)  Microsoft Office Desktop Application  TOEFL ITP |  |   | Surabaya<br>Surabaya<br>Surabaya<br>Surabaya<br>Malang |
| LANGUAGES     | English I<br>TOEFL Score : 473   | Bahasa                                       | Arabic  |  |

#### Hubungi

Cengkareng, Jakarta Barat 082298063323 (Mobile) riskilestaripangestu@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/pangesturl (LinkedIn)

#### Keahlian Teratas

**JavaScript** 

HTML5

Cascading Style Sheets (CSS)

#### Certifications

Awareness Training for HACCP (Hazard Analysis and Critical Control Points)

Best Idea at Techniccal Paper Presentation 3rd National Student Seminar On Agriculture Technology in 2018

1st Indonesian International Invention Festival, I3F 2018 Gold Medal

**TOEFL ITP Test** 

Dasar Pemrograman Web

## Pangestu Riski Lestari

Aspiring Front-End Developer | Belajar dengan Semangat & Fokus pada Pertumbuhan

Jakarta Barat, Jakarta Raya, Indonesia

#### Ringkasan

Saat ini, saya sedang mendalami dunia front-end development melalui bootcamp intensif. Saya berkomitmen untuk membangun kemampuan saya dalam:

JavaScript: Dasar yang kuat untuk pengembangan web interaktif. TypeScript: Untuk kode yang lebih terstruktur dan dapat diskalakan. React.js: Framework modern yang membantu menciptakan pengalaman pengguna yang dinamis dan responsif. Dengan latar belakang dan semangat belajar, saya berambisi untuk memberikan solusi kreatif dan efisien dalam dunia pengembangan web.

Saya percaya bahwa kombinasi antara keterampilan teknis, dedikasi, dan rasa ingin tahu adalah kunci untuk sukses di industri teknologi.

#### Pengalaman

PT Suri Nusantara Jaya Administrative Officer Februari 2022 - Oktober 2023 (1 tahun 9 bulan) Indonesia

- Mengelola dokumen, seperti laporan keuangan, catatan harian
- Melakukan input data, mengarsip, dan merekap data yang masuk

Laboratorium Teknik Pengolahan Pangan dan Hasil Pertanian, Universitas Brawijaya Laboratory Assistant November 2018 - November 2018 (1 bulan) Malang, Jawa Timur, Indonesia

Memandu dan mendampingi mahasiswa selama pelaksanaan praktikum Biomaterial, serta memberikan penilaian terhadap mahasiswa

## Laboratorium Daya dan Mesin Pertanian Universitas Brawijaya Laboratory Assistant

September 2018 - September 2018 (1 bulan)

Malang, Jawa Timur, Indonesia

Memandu dan mendampingi mahasiswa selama pelaksanaan praktikum Kekuatan Bahan, serta memberikan penilaian terhadap mahasiswa

# Indofood Sukses Makmur Tbk, Division Bogasari Flour Mills Mill Operator

Juli 2018 - Juli 2018 (1 bulan)

Jakarta Utara, Jakarta Raya, Indonesia

1. Membuat laporan magang berdasarkan data yang didapatkan dan hasil analisa

yang telah dilakukan.

Melakukan pengujian ukuran granula secara berkala hasil tepung di Mill F dan G

menggunakan mini sifter.

3. Mengantar sampel tepung ke laboratorium untuk pengecekan kualitas tepung yang

dihasilkan oleh Mill F dan G

# Laboratorium Mekatronika Universitas Brawijaya Laboratory Assistant

Oktober 2017 - Oktober 2017 (1 bulan)

Malang, Jawa Timur, Indonesia

Memandu dan mendampingi mahasiswa selama pelaksanaan praktikum Pengukuran Lingkungan / Elektronika dan Instrumentasi, serta memberikan penilaian terhadap mahasiswa

# Laboratorium Fisika Dasar Universitas Brawijaya Laboratory Assistant

November 2016 - November 2016 (1 bulan)

Malang, Jawa Timur, Indonesia

Memandu dan mendampingi mahasiswa selama pelaksanaan praktikum fisika dasar, serta memberikan penilaian terhadap mahasiswa

#### Pendidikan

Universitas Brawijaya

Bachelor's degree, Teknik Pertanian · (Agustus 2015 - Agustus 2019)